Fear, excitement, and thrills-the triple package!
That's me, "Pandæmonium"!
"Pandemonium"? The same name as the prison of fog...
It was my name to begin with,
before they started calling the fog that.
The Ivory one made the fog, not me.
So don't get that mixed up, okay?
I see, so you're simply the Pure Concept of Chaos, then.
Yup, exactly!
Then shall we get this movie started?
Episode 11:
Pandæmonium
I sense a bit of the Ivory one in you.
That's odd.
First, that hole!
I have to close that gate to the
dimension of original sin!
Etheric Connect-Scripture,
12:1-Invoke
[Hammer in, hammer in,
so as to fortify.]
Maa! Amazing!
Invoke
[Thread]
M-maa, oh no! You've captured me so easily!
After all, of the Four Major Human Errors I'm the weakest,
but I'm also known as the worst of the lot:
Pandæmonium!
An illusion? No, I can sense they're both real!
Jeez! I can't believe I'd get tripped up so easily.
I'm so useless!
I'm sorry. I'm weak.
I know that! I'm me too, after all!
There!
Great work on the warm-up match, Miss!
We haven't met in this instance of Time yet,
but let me just say this...
I hate you, Momo.
You always try to keep Menou for yourself.
Still...
Etheric Connect-ImPr•–?cHmnt,
Pure Concept [Time]-Invoke [Regression
Hang in there. Don't die, okay?
You live up to your name as the source of original sin.
It makes sense that you used Manon Libelle
in an attempt to spread monstrine.
Monstrine is made from your blood.
By making people ingest a part of you,
you infested their bodies to use them
as sacrifices for your resurrection.
Half of that isn't right, Miss.
I didn't want to resurrect myself.
I just wanted to try doing a movie!
"Doing... a movie"?
Like I said, I love watching movies!
But you know, there aren't any movies in this world.
I couldn't ignore that, so I'm doing one!
So yeah, I want you to be the heroine of this panic film!
All you need to do is desperately run
to-and-fro away from me, a.k.a. the monster!
What could you possibly gain
from doing something like that?!
No gain. That's not the point.
See, humans are fun to watch when
they're trying their absolute best,
whether they live or die!
What's important is the process.
Watching people doing their best
and dying is so, sooooo...
...much fun!
Who do you think you are?!
I mean, that's what B movies are all about.
Some sudden calamity happens,
there are heaps of victims,
occasionally the main character dies,
humanity goes extinct,
and sometimes it even ends
with the monster winning!
But I think that's the truth, in a way.
After all, isn't reality...
beyond one's control, just like a monster?
Ether: Living Sacrifice-Chaos Adhesion,
Pure Concept [Chaos]-
Summon [Squeak squeak, dig here!]
Come now, Miss!
I oversee the mass of monsters
infesting the eternal world!
If you say you can stop a monster like me,
go ahead and try!
What in the world happened to him?
He was used as a sacrifice in sin magecraft.
I sensed a large, twisted conjuring earlier.
We've received word that there are people
who have melted all over the city!
Those who had been taking monstrine, no doubt.
Go quickly and get information on how many.
Right!
What's going on over there?
[Thou shalt know that
walls surrounding pious
sheep shall never crumble.]
Etheric Connect-Scripture,
2:5-Invoke
Maa, how aggravating!
There, eat up!
[Kneel before the front gate,
for its path leads to the Lord.]
Etheric Connect-Scripture,
8:12-Invoke
A triple invocation of scripture magecraft!
That's very skillful,
but you have pretty mediocre etheric capacity.
You're already almost out.
So that thing is what caused a
hundred people to melt away?
You...!
I'll act as if we're meeting for the first time, Miss Priestess.
I'm Ashuna Grisarika.
What are you fighting against?
One of the Four Major Human Errors, Pandemonium.
I see.
Your Highness...
You just mentioned that a hundred
people melted away.
Indeed.
Though we may not have accounted for all of them.
That number is probably...
the number of lives that thing has.
So we must kill it a hundred times to defeat it?
Nice and clear-cut.
Or perhaps, we may be able to take it out in one blow...
...with Your Highness's help.
Oh?
Maa, maa! We have a new guest, I see!
But with my hands gone,
I can't welcome you with a handshake.
That's her?
I see, the worst possible encounter, indeed.
So? Are you truly up to the task?
Yes, I can definitely do it!
Interesting!
Then go ahead and prove it!
Invoke
[Slash: Expansion]
Ordinarily, humans cannot use power that
goes beyond their etheric capacity.
However...
She connected the earthen and heavenly veins.
What impressive etheric control!
Maa! I really do think you're like the Ivory one,
just a tiny little bit.
Etheric Connect-1:2 Full Passage-Invoke
Beyond the mountains,
there was nothing to be found in the plains
below. Morning, afternoon, and night.
The exhausted people were at a loss.
Blam, blam.
A sound echoed,
and the people raised their heads.
The woman said nothing.
Mouth closed,
she raised her hand
and struck with a hammer.
All eyes were focused
on the woman.
In order to do what must be done,
the woman raised her arm.
She simply hammered the stake,
to make known the land where all shall begin.
A pseudo-church, huh? Wow, just wow!
I think your efforts are victorious-!
Did that do it?
Yes...
I connected the ether of the earthen vein
to the heavenly vein in an endless cycle,
so this binding force is practically permanent.
In all honesty...
It helped that there weren't too many sacrifices.
I wouldn't have managed without Your Highness's help.
I truly appreciate it.
Don't mention it. I'm glad I got to watch.
That was some amazing magecraft.
By the way, well...
Is Momo all right?
We were actually supposed to meet last night,
to compare what we had accomplished.
But she never came.
Momo... was poisoned during an investigation.
What?!
And? How is she?!
I can't say she's doing well, but she should live.
For now, she's at the church-
M-Menou!
No, no.
Not you!
It would be no fun if you went there.
Stay here and play with me!
You're...
Thank you, Your Highness Princess Ashuna.
No thanks necessary.
You should save your ether for later.
In any case...
The size of that thing is beyond ridiculous.
Yoo-hoo!
What do you think?
She's one of my favorites!
Isn't she cute?
She's definitely one of the Four Major Human Errors...
Indeed. A true monstrosity.
Maa, that's awful! A monstrosity?!
I'm a cute little monster!
What are you?
Maa! Should I introduce myself?
She's stopped... isn't she?
Do you understand now?
I'm one of Four Major Human Errors,
the Pure Concept of Chaos.
Why are you getting in my way?!
Because if you go there the movie
will become something different!
After I went through the trouble of summoning that cutie.
You know, this one's super duper strong!
Because she fortified herself through
cannibalism for a looong time in the fog!
"Cannibalism"?
Yup!
So this one's just a bit different
from the ones from before!
So... are you two ready?
Then if I defeat you here,
will that monster disappear too?
Maa! Maa, maa!
You, defeat me?!
I may be weak, but you're even weaker.
You silly, overconfident user of Time.
But if you still don't mind, let's get started!
Boo!
You see now, right? You're no match for me.
That kind of fight scene is just boring in a movie,
don't you think?
Then what did you come here for?
Let's see...
What if I said I wanted to talk with
someone from my homeland?
About something nostalgic from Japan!
No way!
You're a Human Error, aren't you?
You must have used your
Pure Concept so many times
you can't possibly have any memories left!
Maa! I'm impressed you know that!
Every time you use a Pure Concept,
it erodes your soul.
I still want to hear about it, though!
The things you remember,
and your precious memories from Japan-
I don't want them!
I don't want my old world.
I...
I've forgotten a lot already.
But I remember the feeling that
the world was good for nothing.
Note: A vase of flowers on a desk is usually for a dead student
(i.e. Akari was being bullied)
Is a world like that really worth anything?
Oh! But of course it is!
The world doesn't exist for your sake, you know.
We exist for the sake of the world!
Anyway, none of that matters.
To tell you the truth, I just came to thank you.
Thank me?
Yup!
Because I was able to escape
that fog all thanks to you!
Thanks... to me?
I suppose we should start by slicing up this tentacle!
No, Princess Ashuna. There's no need for that.
What? Then what do we do?
There's no need to do anything. Look, there it is.
This monster is still sealed within the prison of fog.
I imagine it's only been summoned temporarily.
Maa! I'm surprised you figured it out, Miss!
I guess I can't bring her out completely just yet.
And now the fog has found me, too!
Pandemonium...
You're not the real one, are you?
Maa! What gave me away?
Except for that massive one,
the monsters you've summoned
aren't particularly strong.
And just look at the state of your
precious minion over there.
If a monster that serves you is still trapped in the fog,
there's no way you could have escaped yourself.
The you here... is just a little portion, isn't it?
That's right, I'm just a finger puppet.
I somehow managed to squeeze just a
pinky finger out through a gap in
the fog when it got warped,
and gave it human form.
A "gap"?
Why would there be such a
thing in the prison of fog?!
Hmm, I can't tell you that.
But Miss Priestess, you alone might understand why!
Could it be... it has to do with Akari?
You know how you turned back time?
On this world,
over and over and over and ooover?
I heard it in the fog, you know.
The sound of you regressing time and
making the world creak under the stress!
That's what warped the fog too, and made a gap.
And I was able to get a pinky out.
You mean-
The stuff happening in this city are
totally aaaall because of you!
I wish you could warp it even more
so that all of me can escape,
but I guess that isn't possible.
You've lost too much of your memories, after all.
If you want to stay intact,
you're at the point where you need to
refrain from using your Pure Concept at all.
I mean, you've forgotten
so much that your personality
isn't what it was like in Japan anymore, right?
So what? I don't care about that.
I have a best friend in this world
I'd be happy to risk my life for!
A friend so precious,
I don't care if I lose all my memories
as long as I remember her!
Maa?
Get out of my way!
All I care about is getting killed by Menou!
I won't become like you...
I won't become a Human Error!
You don't mind getting killed by her?
What a beautiful friendship!
But I feel sorry for you.
You don't realize you're at a dead end.
You really believe that there's a way out.
But there is! Why wouldn't there be?!
That's what this power is for!
No. You'll never make it.
Because to the people who can
connect to the Astral Archive,
your Regression means nothing.
"Astral... Archive"?
Yup...
The memories of this planet and what powers ether.
The origin of the Lord written about
in the priestesses' scriptures.
There's no way to cheat it.
Even up to this point,
it's no accident you kept failing, you know.
Someone used their power to make sure you failed.
"Someone"...?
You have an idea of who it might be?
It's probably that person who
keeps getting in your way.
So listen, here's something you'll want to know.
It exists. A way back to Japan.
This was all caused by Akari?
So now there's yet another reason why
I have to kill her as soon as possible.
But for now, I have to defeat her!
Maa! With the fog surrounding me,
I guess this body is done for.
It lasted longer than expected, though.
Anyway, that's fine.
Let's move on to the next scene!
The classic ending trope!
The big bad uses all its energy to become enormous!
I'm going to put all of the sacrifices
I got in this city towards it!
Come! It's time for the blood-stirring,
flesh-splattering climax!
Next Episode
The Duo's Journey
Next episode: The Duo's Journey.